const prototypes = [
    {
    "question": "What does Array.prototype.length returns?",
    "options":["length of an array", "length of string", "length of an object", "number of elements in array"],
    "answer" : "number of elements in array",
    "points" : 10,
    "key": 1
    },
    {
    "question": "What does Array.prototype.pop() remove?",
    "options":["first element of an array", "last element of an array", "middle element of an array", "first and last element of an array"],
    "answer" : "last element of an array",
    "points" : 10,
    "key": 2
    },
    {
    "question": "What type of prototype method is Array.prototype.push()?",
    "options":["Accessor method", "Mutator method", "Both", "None of these"],
    "answer" : "Mutator method",
    "points" : 10,
    "key": 3
    },
    {
    "question": "What type of prototype method is Array.prototype.reverse()?",
    "options":["Accessor method", "Mutator method", "Both", "None of these"],
    "answer" : "Mutator",
    "points" : 10,
    "key": 4
    },
    {
    "question": "What does Array.prototype.splice() do?",
    "options":["Removes element", "Add elements", "Both", "None of these"],
    "answer" : "Both",
    "points" : 10,
    "key": 5
    },
    {
    "question": "What does Array.prototype.length return?",
    "options":["length of an array", "length of string", "length of an object", "number of elements in array"],
    "answer" : "number of elements in array",
    "points" : 10,
    "key": 6
    },
    {
    "question": "What does Array.prototype.filter return?",
    "options":["Object", "String", "Array", "None of these"],
    "answer" : "Object",
    "points" : 10,
    "key": 7
    },
    {
    "question": "What does Array.prototype.forEach() return?",
    "options":["undefined", "Array", "String", "None of these"],
    "answer" : "undefined",
    "points" : 10,
    "key": 8
    },
    {
    "question": "What prototype method would you use to get a single value from multiple data types?",
    "options":["foreach()", "filter()", "map()", "reduce()"],
    "answer" : "reduce()",
    "points" : 10,
    "key": 9
    },
    {
    "question": "What type of method is Array.prototype.reduce()?",
    "options":["Mutator", "Accessor", "Iterator", "None of these"],
    "answer" : "Iterator",
    "points" : 10,
    "key": 10
    } 

]
export default prototypes;